<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<?metadataRepository version='1.1.0'?>
<repository name='TychoTargetPlatform' type='org.eclipse.equinox.internal.p2.metadata.repository.LocalMetadataRepository' version='0.0.1'>
  <units size='12'>
    <unit id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.source' version='1.0.0.201711031739' singleton='false'>
      <update id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.source' range='[0.0.0,1.0.0.201711031739)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='9'>
        <property name='df_LT.bundleVendor' value='Fraunhofer FOKUS'/>
        <property name='df_LT.bundleName' value='Xtenders Source'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%bundleName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%bundleVendor'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.bundle.localization' value='OSGI-INF/l10n/bundle-src'/>
        <property name='maven-groupId' value='de.fhg.fokus'/>
        <property name='maven-artifactId' value='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions'/>
        <property name='maven-version' value='1.0.0-SNAPSHOT'/>
        <property name='maven-classifier' value='sources'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='4'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.source' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.source' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='source' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.source' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.source&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.0.0.201711031739
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.source.feature.jar' version='1.0.0.201711031739'>
      <properties size='8'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='Xtensions Feature Developer Resources'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='This library provides utility extension methods, mostly for JDK 8 classes.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='https://github.com/fraunhoferfokus/Xtensions'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='de.fhg.fokus'/>
        <property name='maven-groupId' value='de.fhg.fokus'/>
        <property name='maven-artifactId' value='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature'/>
        <property name='maven-version' value='1.0.0-SNAPSHOT'/>
        <property name='maven-classifier' value='sources-feature'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.source.feature.jar' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.source' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.source' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='https://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v20.html' url='https://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v20.html'>
          Eclipse Public License - v 2.0&#xA;&#xA;    THE ACCOMPANYING PROGRAM IS PROVIDED UNDER THE TERMS OF THIS ECLIPSE&#xA;    PUBLIC LICENSE (&amp;quot;AGREEMENT&amp;quot;). ANY USE, REPRODUCTION OR DISTRIBUTION&#xA;    OF THE PROGRAM CONSTITUTES RECIPIENT&amp;apos;S ACCEPTANCE OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;&#xA;1. DEFINITIONS&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Contribution&amp;quot; means:&#xA;&#xA;  a) in the case of the initial Contributor, the initial content&#xA;     Distributed under this Agreement, and&#xA;&#xA;  b) in the case of each subsequent Contributor:&#xA;     i) changes to the Program, and&#xA;     ii) additions to the Program;&#xA;  where such changes and/or additions to the Program originate from&#xA;  and are Distributed by that particular Contributor. A Contribution&#xA;  &amp;quot;originates&amp;quot; from a Contributor if it was added to the Program by&#xA;  such Contributor itself or anyone acting on such Contributor&amp;apos;s behalf.&#xA;  Contributions do not include changes or additions to the Program that&#xA;  are not Modified Works.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Contributor&amp;quot; means any person or entity that Distributes the Program.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Licensed Patents&amp;quot; mean patent claims licensable by a Contributor which&#xA;are necessarily infringed by the use or sale of its Contribution alone&#xA;or when combined with the Program.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Program&amp;quot; means the Contributions Distributed in accordance with this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Recipient&amp;quot; means anyone who receives the Program under this Agreement&#xA;or any Secondary License (as applicable), including Contributors.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Derivative Works&amp;quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source Code or other&#xA;form, that is based on (or derived from) the Program and for which the&#xA;editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications&#xA;represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Modified Works&amp;quot; shall mean any work in Source Code or other form that&#xA;results from an addition to, deletion from, or modification of the&#xA;contents of the Program, including, for purposes of clarity any new file&#xA;in Source Code form that contains any contents of the Program. Modified&#xA;Works shall not include works that contain only declarations,&#xA;interfaces, types, classes, structures, or files of the Program solely&#xA;in each case in order to link to, bind by name, or subclass the Program&#xA;or Modified Works thereof.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Distribute&amp;quot; means the acts of a) distributing or b) making available&#xA;in any manner that enables the transfer of a copy.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Source Code&amp;quot; means the form of a Program preferred for making&#xA;modifications, including but not limited to software source code,&#xA;documentation source, and configuration files.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Secondary License&amp;quot; means either the GNU General Public License,&#xA;Version 2.0, or any later versions of that license, including any&#xA;exceptions or additional permissions as identified by the initial&#xA;Contributor.&#xA;&#xA;2. GRANT OF RIGHTS&#xA;&#xA;  a) Subject to the terms of this Agreement, each Contributor hereby&#xA;  grants Recipient a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free copyright&#xA;  license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of, publicly display,&#xA;  publicly perform, Distribute and sublicense the Contribution of such&#xA;  Contributor, if any, and such Derivative Works.&#xA;&#xA;  b) Subject to the terms of this Agreement, each Contributor hereby&#xA;  grants Recipient a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free patent&#xA;  license under Licensed Patents to make, use, sell, offer to sell,&#xA;  import and otherwise transfer the Contribution of such Contributor,&#xA;  if any, in Source Code or other form. This patent license shall&#xA;  apply to the combination of the Contribution and the Program if, at&#xA;  the time the Contribution is added by the Contributor, such addition&#xA;  of the Contribution causes such combination to be covered by the&#xA;  Licensed Patents. The patent license shall not apply to any other&#xA;  combinations which include the Contribution. No hardware per se is&#xA;  licensed hereunder.&#xA;&#xA;  c) Recipient understands that although each Contributor grants the&#xA;  licenses to its Contributions set forth herein, no assurances are&#xA;  provided by any Contributor that the Program does not infringe the&#xA;  patent or other intellectual property rights of any other entity.&#xA;  Each Contributor disclaims any liability to Recipient for claims&#xA;  brought by any other entity based on infringement of intellectual&#xA;  property rights or otherwise. As a condition to exercising the&#xA;  rights and licenses granted hereunder, each Recipient hereby&#xA;  assumes sole responsibility to secure any other intellectual&#xA;  property rights needed, if any. For example, if a third party&#xA;  patent license is required to allow Recipient to Distribute the&#xA;  Program, it is Recipient&amp;apos;s responsibility to acquire that license&#xA;  before distributing the Program.&#xA;&#xA;  d) Each Contributor represents that to its knowledge it has&#xA;  sufficient copyright rights in its Contribution, if any, to grant&#xA;  the copyright license set forth in this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;  e) Notwithstanding the terms of any Secondary License, no&#xA;  Contributor makes additional grants to any Recipient (other than&#xA;  those set forth in this Agreement) as a result of such Recipient&amp;apos;s&#xA;  receipt of the Program under the terms of a Secondary License&#xA;  (if permitted under the terms of Section 3).&#xA;&#xA;3. REQUIREMENTS&#xA;&#xA;3.1 If a Contributor Distributes the Program in any form, then:&#xA;&#xA;  a) the Program must also be made available as Source Code, in&#xA;  accordance with section 3.2, and the Contributor must accompany&#xA;  the Program with a statement that the Source Code for the Program&#xA;  is available under this Agreement, and informs Recipients how to&#xA;  obtain it in a reasonable manner on or through a medium customarily&#xA;  used for software exchange; and&#xA;&#xA;  b) the Contributor may Distribute the Program under a license&#xA;  different than this Agreement, provided that such license:&#xA;     i) effectively disclaims on behalf of all other Contributors all&#xA;     warranties and conditions, express and implied, including&#xA;     warranties or conditions of title and non-infringement, and&#xA;     implied warranties or conditions of merchantability and fitness&#xA;     for a particular purpose;&#xA;&#xA;     ii) effectively excludes on behalf of all other Contributors all&#xA;     liability for damages, including direct, indirect, special,&#xA;     incidental and consequential damages, such as lost profits;&#xA;&#xA;     iii) does not attempt to limit or alter the recipients&amp;apos; rights&#xA;     in the Source Code under section 3.2; and&#xA;&#xA;     iv) requires any subsequent distribution of the Program by any&#xA;     party to be under a license that satisfies the requirements&#xA;     of this section 3.&#xA;&#xA;3.2 When the Program is Distributed as Source Code:&#xA;&#xA;  a) it must be made available under this Agreement, or if the&#xA;  Program (i) is combined with other material in a separate file or&#xA;  files made available under a Secondary License, and (ii) the initial&#xA;  Contributor attached to the Source Code the notice described in&#xA;  Exhibit A of this Agreement, then the Program may be made available&#xA;  under the terms of such Secondary Licenses, and&#xA;&#xA;  b) a copy of this Agreement must be included with each copy of&#xA;  the Program.&#xA;&#xA;3.3 Contributors may not remove or alter any copyright, patent,&#xA;trademark, attribution notices, disclaimers of warranty, or limitations&#xA;of liability (&amp;quot;notices&amp;quot;) contained within the Program from any copy of&#xA;the Program which they Distribute, provided that Contributors may add&#xA;their own appropriate notices.&#xA;&#xA;4. COMMERCIAL DISTRIBUTION&#xA;&#xA;Commercial distributors of software may accept certain responsibilities&#xA;with respect to end users, business partners and the like. While this&#xA;license is intended to facilitate the commercial use of the Program,&#xA;the Contributor who includes the Program in a commercial product&#xA;offering should do so in a manner which does not create potential&#xA;liability for other Contributors. Therefore, if a Contributor includes&#xA;the Program in a commercial product offering, such Contributor&#xA;(&amp;quot;Commercial Contributor&amp;quot;) hereby agrees to defend and indemnify every&#xA;other Contributor (&amp;quot;Indemnified Contributor&amp;quot;) against any losses,&#xA;damages and costs (collectively &amp;quot;Losses&amp;quot;) arising from claims, lawsuits&#xA;and other legal actions brought by a third party against the Indemnified&#xA;Contributor to the extent caused by the acts or omissions of such&#xA;Commercial Contributor in connection with its distribution of the Program&#xA;in a commercial product offering. The obligations in this section do not&#xA;apply to any claims or Losses relating to any actual or alleged&#xA;intellectual property infringement. In order to qualify, an Indemnified&#xA;Contributor must: a) promptly notify the Commercial Contributor in&#xA;writing of such claim, and b) allow the Commercial Contributor to control,&#xA;and cooperate with the Commercial Contributor in, the defense and any&#xA;related settlement negotiations. The Indemnified Contributor may&#xA;participate in any such claim at its own expense.&#xA;&#xA;For example, a Contributor might include the Program in a commercial&#xA;product offering, Product X. That Contributor is then a Commercial&#xA;Contributor. If that Commercial Contributor then makes performance&#xA;claims, or offers warranties related to Product X, those performance&#xA;claims and warranties are such Commercial Contributor&amp;apos;s responsibility&#xA;alone. Under this section, the Commercial Contributor would have to&#xA;defend claims against the other Contributors related to those performance&#xA;claims and warranties, and if a court requires any other Contributor to&#xA;pay any damages as a result, the Commercial Contributor must pay&#xA;those damages.&#xA;&#xA;5. NO WARRANTY&#xA;&#xA;EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH IN THIS AGREEMENT, AND TO THE EXTENT&#xA;PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE PROGRAM IS PROVIDED ON AN &amp;quot;AS IS&amp;quot;&#xA;BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR&#xA;IMPLIED INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF&#xA;TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR&#xA;PURPOSE. Each Recipient is solely responsible for determining the&#xA;appropriateness of using and distributing the Program and assumes all&#xA;risks associated with its exercise of rights under this Agreement,&#xA;including but not limited to the risks and costs of program errors,&#xA;compliance with applicable laws, damage to or loss of data, programs&#xA;or equipment, and unavailability or interruption of operations.&#xA;&#xA;6. DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY&#xA;&#xA;EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH IN THIS AGREEMENT, AND TO THE EXTENT&#xA;PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, NEITHER RECIPIENT NOR ANY CONTRIBUTORS&#xA;SHALL HAVE ANY LIABILITY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL,&#xA;EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LOST&#xA;PROFITS), HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN&#xA;CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE)&#xA;ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OR DISTRIBUTION OF THE PROGRAM OR THE&#xA;EXERCISE OF ANY RIGHTS GRANTED HEREUNDER, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE&#xA;POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.&#xA;&#xA;7. GENERAL&#xA;&#xA;If any provision of this Agreement is invalid or unenforceable under&#xA;applicable law, it shall not affect the validity or enforceability of&#xA;the remainder of the terms of this Agreement, and without further&#xA;action by the parties hereto, such provision shall be reformed to the&#xA;minimum extent necessary to make such provision valid and enforceable.&#xA;&#xA;If Recipient institutes patent litigation against any entity&#xA;(including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the&#xA;Program itself (excluding combinations of the Program with other software&#xA;or hardware) infringes such Recipient&amp;apos;s patent(s), then such Recipient&amp;apos;s&#xA;rights granted under Section 2(b) shall terminate as of the date such&#xA;litigation is filed.&#xA;&#xA;All Recipient&amp;apos;s rights under this Agreement shall terminate if it&#xA;fails to comply with any of the material terms or conditions of this&#xA;Agreement and does not cure such failure in a reasonable period of&#xA;time after becoming aware of such noncompliance. If all Recipient&amp;apos;s&#xA;rights under this Agreement terminate, Recipient agrees to cease use&#xA;and distribution of the Program as soon as reasonably practicable.&#xA;However, Recipient&amp;apos;s obligations under this Agreement and any licenses&#xA;granted by Recipient relating to the Program shall continue and survive.&#xA;&#xA;Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute copies of this Agreement,&#xA;but in order to avoid inconsistency the Agreement is copyrighted and&#xA;may only be modified in the following manner. The Agreement Steward&#xA;reserves the right to publish new versions (including revisions) of&#xA;this Agreement from time to time. No one other than the Agreement&#xA;Steward has the right to modify this Agreement. The Eclipse Foundation&#xA;is the initial Agreement Steward. The Eclipse Foundation may assign the&#xA;responsibility to serve as the Agreement Steward to a suitable separate&#xA;entity. Each new version of the Agreement will be given a distinguishing&#xA;version number. The Program (including Contributions) may always be&#xA;Distributed subject to the version of the Agreement under which it was&#xA;received. In addition, after a new version of the Agreement is published,&#xA;Contributor may elect to Distribute the Program (including its&#xA;Contributions) under the new version.&#xA;&#xA;Except as expressly stated in Sections 2(a) and 2(b) above, Recipient&#xA;receives no rights or licenses to the intellectual property of any&#xA;Contributor under this Agreement, whether expressly, by implication,&#xA;estoppel or otherwise. All rights in the Program not expressly granted&#xA;under this Agreement are reserved. Nothing in this Agreement is intended&#xA;to be enforceable by any entity that is not a Contributor or Recipient.&#xA;No third-party beneficiary rights are created under this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;Exhibit A - Form of Secondary Licenses Notice&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;This Source Code may also be made available under the following &#xA;Secondary Licenses when the conditions for such availability set forth &#xA;in the Eclipse Public License, v. 2.0 are satisfied: {name license(s),&#xA;version(s), and exceptions or additional permissions here}.&amp;quot;&#xA;&#xA;  Simply including a copy of this Agreement, including this Exhibit A&#xA;  is not sufficient to license the Source Code under Secondary Licenses.&#xA;&#xA;  If it is not possible or desirable to put the notice in a particular&#xA;  file, then You may include the notice in a location (such as a LICENSE&#xA;  file in a relevant directory) where a recipient would be likely to&#xA;  look for such a notice.&#xA;&#xA;  You may add additional accurate notices of copyright ownership.
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='https://github.com/fraunhoferfokus/Xtensions' url='https://github.com/fraunhoferfokus/Xtensions'>
        Copyright (c) 2017 Max Bureck (Fraunhofer FOKUS) and others.&#xA;All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials&#xA;are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v2.0&#xA;which accompanies this distribution, and is available at&#xA;http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v20.html&#xA;&#xA;Contributors:&#xA;Max Bureck (Fraunhofer FOKUS)
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.eclipse.xtext.xbase.lib' version='2.12.0.v20170518-0757' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.eclipse.xtext.xbase.lib' range='[0.0.0,2.12.0.v20170518-0757)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='Xbase Runtime Library'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='Eclipse Xtext'/>
        <property name='maven-groupId' value='org.eclipse.xtext'/>
        <property name='maven-artifactId' value='org.eclipse.xtext.xbase.lib'/>
        <property name='maven-version' value='2.12.0'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='7'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.xtext.xbase.lib' version='2.12.0.v20170518-0757'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.xtext.xbase.lib' version='2.12.0.v20170518-0757'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.eclipse.xtend2.lib' version='2.12.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.eclipse.xtext.xbase.lib' version='2.12.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.eclipse.xtext.xbase.lib.internal' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.eclipse.xtext.xbase.lib.util' version='2.12.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='1'>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.google.guava' range='[14.0.0,22.0.0)'/>
      </requires>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.eclipse.xtext.xbase.lib' version='2.12.0.v20170518-0757'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: org.eclipse.xtext.xbase.lib&#xA;Bundle-Version: 2.12.0.v20170518-0757
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='a.jre.javase' version='1.7.0' singleton='false'>
      <provides size='174'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='a.jre.javase' version='1.7.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.accessibility' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.activation' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.activity' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.annotation' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.annotation.processing' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.crypto' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.crypto.interfaces' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.crypto.spec' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.imageio' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.imageio.event' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.imageio.metadata' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.imageio.plugins.bmp' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.imageio.plugins.jpeg' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.imageio.spi' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.imageio.stream' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.jws' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.jws.soap' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.lang.model' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.lang.model.element' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.lang.model.type' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.lang.model.util' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.management' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.management.loading' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.management.modelmbean' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.management.monitor' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.management.openmbean' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.management.relation' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.management.remote' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.management.remote.rmi' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.management.timer' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.naming' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.naming.directory' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.naming.event' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.naming.ldap' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.naming.spi' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.net' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.net.ssl' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.print' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.print.attribute' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.print.attribute.standard' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.print.event' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.rmi' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.rmi.CORBA' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.rmi.ssl' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.script' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.security.auth' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.security.auth.callback' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.security.auth.kerberos' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.security.auth.login' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.security.auth.spi' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.security.auth.x500' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.security.cert' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.security.sasl' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.sound.midi' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.sound.midi.spi' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.sound.sampled' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.sound.sampled.spi' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.sql' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.sql.rowset' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.sql.rowset.serial' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.sql.rowset.spi' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.border' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.colorchooser' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.event' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.filechooser' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.plaf' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.plaf.basic' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.plaf.metal' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.plaf.multi' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.plaf.nimbus' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.plaf.synth' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.table' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.text' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.text.html' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.text.html.parser' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.text.rtf' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.tree' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.swing.undo' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.tools' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.transaction' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.transaction.xa' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.bind' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.bind.annotation' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.bind.annotation.adapters' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.bind.attachment' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.bind.helpers' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.bind.util' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.crypto' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.crypto.dom' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.crypto.dsig' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.crypto.dsig.dom' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.crypto.dsig.keyinfo' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.crypto.dsig.spec' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.datatype' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.namespace' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.parsers' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.soap' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.stream' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.stream.events' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.stream.util' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.transform' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.transform.dom' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.transform.sax' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.transform.stax' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.transform.stream' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.validation' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.ws' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.ws.handler' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.ws.handler.soap' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.ws.http' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.ws.soap' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.ws.spi' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.ws.spi.http' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.ws.wsaddressing' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='javax.xml.xpath' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.ietf.jgss' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.CORBA' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.CORBA_2_3' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.CORBA_2_3.portable' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.CORBA.DynAnyPackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.CORBA.ORBPackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.CORBA.portable' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.CORBA.TypeCodePackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.CosNaming' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.CosNaming.NamingContextExtPackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.CosNaming.NamingContextPackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.Dynamic' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.DynamicAny' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.DynamicAny.DynAnyFactoryPackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.DynamicAny.DynAnyPackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.IOP' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.IOP.CodecFactoryPackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.IOP.CodecPackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.Messaging' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.PortableInterceptor' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.PortableInterceptor.ORBInitInfoPackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.PortableServer' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.PortableServer.CurrentPackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.PortableServer.POAManagerPackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.PortableServer.POAPackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.PortableServer.portable' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.PortableServer.ServantLocatorPackage' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.SendingContext' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.omg.stub.java.rmi' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.w3c.dom' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.w3c.dom.bootstrap' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.w3c.dom.css' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.w3c.dom.events' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.w3c.dom.html' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.w3c.dom.ls' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.w3c.dom.ranges' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.w3c.dom.stylesheets' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.w3c.dom.traversal' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.w3c.dom.views' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.w3c.dom.xpath' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.xml.sax' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.xml.sax.ext' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.xml.sax.helpers' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.ee' name='OSGi/Minimum' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.ee' name='OSGi/Minimum' version='1.1.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.ee' name='OSGi/Minimum' version='1.2.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.ee' name='JRE' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.ee' name='JRE' version='1.1.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.ee' name='JavaSE' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.ee' name='JavaSE' version='1.1.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.ee' name='JavaSE' version='1.2.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.ee' name='JavaSE' version='1.3.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.ee' name='JavaSE' version='1.4.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.ee' name='JavaSE' version='1.5.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.ee' name='JavaSE' version='1.6.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.ee' name='JavaSE' version='1.7.0'/>
      </provides>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.native' version='1.0.0'/>
    </unit>
    <unit id='config.a.jre.javase' version='1.7.0' singleton='false'>
      <hostRequirements size='1'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='a.jre.javase' range='1.7.0'/>
      </hostRequirements>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.fragment' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='config.a.jre.javase' version='1.7.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='1'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='a.jre.javase' range='1.7.0'/>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.native' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='install'>

          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.eclipse.xtend.lib' version='2.12.0.v20170518-0757' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.eclipse.xtend.lib' range='[0.0.0,2.12.0.v20170518-0757)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='Xtend Runtime Library'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='Eclipse Xtext'/>
        <property name='maven-groupId' value='org.eclipse.xtend'/>
        <property name='maven-artifactId' value='org.eclipse.xtend.lib'/>
        <property name='maven-version' value='2.12.0'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='5'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.xtend.lib' version='2.12.0.v20170518-0757'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.xtend.lib' version='2.12.0.v20170518-0757'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.eclipse.xtend.lib' version='2.12.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.eclipse.xtend.lib.annotations' version='2.12.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='2'>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.xtext.xbase.lib' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.xtend.lib.macro' range='0.0.0'/>
      </requires>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.eclipse.xtend.lib' version='2.12.0.v20170518-0757'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: org.eclipse.xtend.lib&#xA;Bundle-Version: 2.12.0.v20170518-0757
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.google.guava' version='21.0.0.v20170206-1425' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.google.guava' range='[0.0.0,21.0.0.v20170206-1425)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='12'>
        <property name='df_LT.bundleVendor' value='Eclipse Orbit'/>
        <property name='df_LT.bundleName' value='Guava: Google Core Libraries for Java'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%bundleName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='Guava is a suite of core and expanded libraries that include    utility classes, google&apos;s collections, io classes, and much    much more.    Guava has only one code dependency - javax.annotation,    per the JSR-305 spec.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%bundleVendor'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.doc.url' value='https://github.com/google/guava/'/>
        <property name='maven-groupId' value='org.eclipse.orbit.bundles'/>
        <property name='maven-artifactId' value='com.google.guava'/>
        <property name='maven-version' value='21.0.0-SNAPSHOT'/>
        <property name='iplog.bug_id' value='12630'/>
        <property name='iplog.contact.name' value='Steffen Pingel'/>
        <property name='iplog.contact.email' value='steffen.pingel@tasktop.com'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='22'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.google.guava' version='21.0.0.v20170206-1425'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.google.guava' version='21.0.0.v20170206-1425'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.base.internal' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.annotations' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.base' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.cache' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.collect' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.escape' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.eventbus' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.graph' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.hash' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.html' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.io' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.math' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.net' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.primitives' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.reflect' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.util.concurrent' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.xml' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='com.google.thirdparty.publicsuffix' version='21.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='16'>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.base' range='[21.0.0,22.0.0)'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.cache' range='[21.0.0,22.0.0)'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.collect' range='[21.0.0,22.0.0)'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.escape' range='[21.0.0,22.0.0)'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.hash' range='[21.0.0,22.0.0)'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.io' range='[21.0.0,22.0.0)'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.math' range='[21.0.0,22.0.0)'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.primitives' range='[21.0.0,22.0.0)'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.reflect' range='[21.0.0,22.0.0)'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='com.google.common.util.concurrent' range='[21.0.0,22.0.0)'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='com.google.errorprone.annotations.concurrent' range='0.0.0' optional='true' greedy='false'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='com.google.thirdparty.publicsuffix' range='[21.0.0,22.0.0)' optional='true' greedy='false'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='javax.annotation' range='0.0.0' optional='true' greedy='false'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='javax.crypto' range='0.0.0' optional='true' greedy='false'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='javax.crypto.spec' range='0.0.0' optional='true' greedy='false'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='sun.misc' range='0.0.0' optional='true' greedy='false'/>
      </requires>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='com.google.guava' version='21.0.0.v20170206-1425'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: com.google.guava&#xA;Bundle-Version: 21.0.0.v20170206-1425
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.feature.jar' version='1.0.0.201711031739'>
      <properties size='7'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='Xtensions Feature'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='This library provides utility extension methods, mostly for JDK 8 classes.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='https://github.com/fraunhoferfokus/Xtensions'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='de.fhg.fokus'/>
        <property name='maven-groupId' value='de.fhg.fokus'/>
        <property name='maven-artifactId' value='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature'/>
        <property name='maven-version' value='1.0.0-SNAPSHOT'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.feature.jar' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='https://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v20.html' url='https://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v20.html'>
          Eclipse Public License - v 2.0&#xA;&#xA;    THE ACCOMPANYING PROGRAM IS PROVIDED UNDER THE TERMS OF THIS ECLIPSE&#xA;    PUBLIC LICENSE (&quot;AGREEMENT&quot;). ANY USE, REPRODUCTION OR DISTRIBUTION&#xA;    OF THE PROGRAM CONSTITUTES RECIPIENT&apos;S ACCEPTANCE OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;&#xA;1. DEFINITIONS&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; means:&#xA;&#xA;  a) in the case of the initial Contributor, the initial content&#xA;     Distributed under this Agreement, and&#xA;&#xA;  b) in the case of each subsequent Contributor:&#xA;     i) changes to the Program, and&#xA;     ii) additions to the Program;&#xA;  where such changes and/or additions to the Program originate from&#xA;  and are Distributed by that particular Contributor. A Contribution&#xA;  &quot;originates&quot; from a Contributor if it was added to the Program by&#xA;  such Contributor itself or anyone acting on such Contributor&apos;s behalf.&#xA;  Contributions do not include changes or additions to the Program that&#xA;  are not Modified Works.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; means any person or entity that Distributes the Program.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Licensed Patents&quot; mean patent claims licensable by a Contributor which&#xA;are necessarily infringed by the use or sale of its Contribution alone&#xA;or when combined with the Program.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Program&quot; means the Contributions Distributed in accordance with this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Recipient&quot; means anyone who receives the Program under this Agreement&#xA;or any Secondary License (as applicable), including Contributors.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source Code or other&#xA;form, that is based on (or derived from) the Program and for which the&#xA;editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications&#xA;represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Modified Works&quot; shall mean any work in Source Code or other form that&#xA;results from an addition to, deletion from, or modification of the&#xA;contents of the Program, including, for purposes of clarity any new file&#xA;in Source Code form that contains any contents of the Program. Modified&#xA;Works shall not include works that contain only declarations,&#xA;interfaces, types, classes, structures, or files of the Program solely&#xA;in each case in order to link to, bind by name, or subclass the Program&#xA;or Modified Works thereof.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Distribute&quot; means the acts of a) distributing or b) making available&#xA;in any manner that enables the transfer of a copy.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Source Code&quot; means the form of a Program preferred for making&#xA;modifications, including but not limited to software source code,&#xA;documentation source, and configuration files.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Secondary License&quot; means either the GNU General Public License,&#xA;Version 2.0, or any later versions of that license, including any&#xA;exceptions or additional permissions as identified by the initial&#xA;Contributor.&#xA;&#xA;2. GRANT OF RIGHTS&#xA;&#xA;  a) Subject to the terms of this Agreement, each Contributor hereby&#xA;  grants Recipient a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free copyright&#xA;  license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of, publicly display,&#xA;  publicly perform, Distribute and sublicense the Contribution of such&#xA;  Contributor, if any, and such Derivative Works.&#xA;&#xA;  b) Subject to the terms of this Agreement, each Contributor hereby&#xA;  grants Recipient a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free patent&#xA;  license under Licensed Patents to make, use, sell, offer to sell,&#xA;  import and otherwise transfer the Contribution of such Contributor,&#xA;  if any, in Source Code or other form. This patent license shall&#xA;  apply to the combination of the Contribution and the Program if, at&#xA;  the time the Contribution is added by the Contributor, such addition&#xA;  of the Contribution causes such combination to be covered by the&#xA;  Licensed Patents. The patent license shall not apply to any other&#xA;  combinations which include the Contribution. No hardware per se is&#xA;  licensed hereunder.&#xA;&#xA;  c) Recipient understands that although each Contributor grants the&#xA;  licenses to its Contributions set forth herein, no assurances are&#xA;  provided by any Contributor that the Program does not infringe the&#xA;  patent or other intellectual property rights of any other entity.&#xA;  Each Contributor disclaims any liability to Recipient for claims&#xA;  brought by any other entity based on infringement of intellectual&#xA;  property rights or otherwise. As a condition to exercising the&#xA;  rights and licenses granted hereunder, each Recipient hereby&#xA;  assumes sole responsibility to secure any other intellectual&#xA;  property rights needed, if any. For example, if a third party&#xA;  patent license is required to allow Recipient to Distribute the&#xA;  Program, it is Recipient&apos;s responsibility to acquire that license&#xA;  before distributing the Program.&#xA;&#xA;  d) Each Contributor represents that to its knowledge it has&#xA;  sufficient copyright rights in its Contribution, if any, to grant&#xA;  the copyright license set forth in this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;  e) Notwithstanding the terms of any Secondary License, no&#xA;  Contributor makes additional grants to any Recipient (other than&#xA;  those set forth in this Agreement) as a result of such Recipient&apos;s&#xA;  receipt of the Program under the terms of a Secondary License&#xA;  (if permitted under the terms of Section 3).&#xA;&#xA;3. REQUIREMENTS&#xA;&#xA;3.1 If a Contributor Distributes the Program in any form, then:&#xA;&#xA;  a) the Program must also be made available as Source Code, in&#xA;  accordance with section 3.2, and the Contributor must accompany&#xA;  the Program with a statement that the Source Code for the Program&#xA;  is available under this Agreement, and informs Recipients how to&#xA;  obtain it in a reasonable manner on or through a medium customarily&#xA;  used for software exchange; and&#xA;&#xA;  b) the Contributor may Distribute the Program under a license&#xA;  different than this Agreement, provided that such license:&#xA;     i) effectively disclaims on behalf of all other Contributors all&#xA;     warranties and conditions, express and implied, including&#xA;     warranties or conditions of title and non-infringement, and&#xA;     implied warranties or conditions of merchantability and fitness&#xA;     for a particular purpose;&#xA;&#xA;     ii) effectively excludes on behalf of all other Contributors all&#xA;     liability for damages, including direct, indirect, special,&#xA;     incidental and consequential damages, such as lost profits;&#xA;&#xA;     iii) does not attempt to limit or alter the recipients&apos; rights&#xA;     in the Source Code under section 3.2; and&#xA;&#xA;     iv) requires any subsequent distribution of the Program by any&#xA;     party to be under a license that satisfies the requirements&#xA;     of this section 3.&#xA;&#xA;3.2 When the Program is Distributed as Source Code:&#xA;&#xA;  a) it must be made available under this Agreement, or if the&#xA;  Program (i) is combined with other material in a separate file or&#xA;  files made available under a Secondary License, and (ii) the initial&#xA;  Contributor attached to the Source Code the notice described in&#xA;  Exhibit A of this Agreement, then the Program may be made available&#xA;  under the terms of such Secondary Licenses, and&#xA;&#xA;  b) a copy of this Agreement must be included with each copy of&#xA;  the Program.&#xA;&#xA;3.3 Contributors may not remove or alter any copyright, patent,&#xA;trademark, attribution notices, disclaimers of warranty, or limitations&#xA;of liability (&quot;notices&quot;) contained within the Program from any copy of&#xA;the Program which they Distribute, provided that Contributors may add&#xA;their own appropriate notices.&#xA;&#xA;4. COMMERCIAL DISTRIBUTION&#xA;&#xA;Commercial distributors of software may accept certain responsibilities&#xA;with respect to end users, business partners and the like. While this&#xA;license is intended to facilitate the commercial use of the Program,&#xA;the Contributor who includes the Program in a commercial product&#xA;offering should do so in a manner which does not create potential&#xA;liability for other Contributors. Therefore, if a Contributor includes&#xA;the Program in a commercial product offering, such Contributor&#xA;(&quot;Commercial Contributor&quot;) hereby agrees to defend and indemnify every&#xA;other Contributor (&quot;Indemnified Contributor&quot;) against any losses,&#xA;damages and costs (collectively &quot;Losses&quot;) arising from claims, lawsuits&#xA;and other legal actions brought by a third party against the Indemnified&#xA;Contributor to the extent caused by the acts or omissions of such&#xA;Commercial Contributor in connection with its distribution of the Program&#xA;in a commercial product offering. The obligations in this section do not&#xA;apply to any claims or Losses relating to any actual or alleged&#xA;intellectual property infringement. In order to qualify, an Indemnified&#xA;Contributor must: a) promptly notify the Commercial Contributor in&#xA;writing of such claim, and b) allow the Commercial Contributor to control,&#xA;and cooperate with the Commercial Contributor in, the defense and any&#xA;related settlement negotiations. The Indemnified Contributor may&#xA;participate in any such claim at its own expense.&#xA;&#xA;For example, a Contributor might include the Program in a commercial&#xA;product offering, Product X. That Contributor is then a Commercial&#xA;Contributor. If that Commercial Contributor then makes performance&#xA;claims, or offers warranties related to Product X, those performance&#xA;claims and warranties are such Commercial Contributor&apos;s responsibility&#xA;alone. Under this section, the Commercial Contributor would have to&#xA;defend claims against the other Contributors related to those performance&#xA;claims and warranties, and if a court requires any other Contributor to&#xA;pay any damages as a result, the Commercial Contributor must pay&#xA;those damages.&#xA;&#xA;5. NO WARRANTY&#xA;&#xA;EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH IN THIS AGREEMENT, AND TO THE EXTENT&#xA;PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE PROGRAM IS PROVIDED ON AN &quot;AS IS&quot;&#xA;BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR&#xA;IMPLIED INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF&#xA;TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR&#xA;PURPOSE. Each Recipient is solely responsible for determining the&#xA;appropriateness of using and distributing the Program and assumes all&#xA;risks associated with its exercise of rights under this Agreement,&#xA;including but not limited to the risks and costs of program errors,&#xA;compliance with applicable laws, damage to or loss of data, programs&#xA;or equipment, and unavailability or interruption of operations.&#xA;&#xA;6. DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY&#xA;&#xA;EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH IN THIS AGREEMENT, AND TO THE EXTENT&#xA;PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, NEITHER RECIPIENT NOR ANY CONTRIBUTORS&#xA;SHALL HAVE ANY LIABILITY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL,&#xA;EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LOST&#xA;PROFITS), HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN&#xA;CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE)&#xA;ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OR DISTRIBUTION OF THE PROGRAM OR THE&#xA;EXERCISE OF ANY RIGHTS GRANTED HEREUNDER, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE&#xA;POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.&#xA;&#xA;7. GENERAL&#xA;&#xA;If any provision of this Agreement is invalid or unenforceable under&#xA;applicable law, it shall not affect the validity or enforceability of&#xA;the remainder of the terms of this Agreement, and without further&#xA;action by the parties hereto, such provision shall be reformed to the&#xA;minimum extent necessary to make such provision valid and enforceable.&#xA;&#xA;If Recipient institutes patent litigation against any entity&#xA;(including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the&#xA;Program itself (excluding combinations of the Program with other software&#xA;or hardware) infringes such Recipient&apos;s patent(s), then such Recipient&apos;s&#xA;rights granted under Section 2(b) shall terminate as of the date such&#xA;litigation is filed.&#xA;&#xA;All Recipient&apos;s rights under this Agreement shall terminate if it&#xA;fails to comply with any of the material terms or conditions of this&#xA;Agreement and does not cure such failure in a reasonable period of&#xA;time after becoming aware of such noncompliance. If all Recipient&apos;s&#xA;rights under this Agreement terminate, Recipient agrees to cease use&#xA;and distribution of the Program as soon as reasonably practicable.&#xA;However, Recipient&apos;s obligations under this Agreement and any licenses&#xA;granted by Recipient relating to the Program shall continue and survive.&#xA;&#xA;Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute copies of this Agreement,&#xA;but in order to avoid inconsistency the Agreement is copyrighted and&#xA;may only be modified in the following manner. The Agreement Steward&#xA;reserves the right to publish new versions (including revisions) of&#xA;this Agreement from time to time. No one other than the Agreement&#xA;Steward has the right to modify this Agreement. The Eclipse Foundation&#xA;is the initial Agreement Steward. The Eclipse Foundation may assign the&#xA;responsibility to serve as the Agreement Steward to a suitable separate&#xA;entity. Each new version of the Agreement will be given a distinguishing&#xA;version number. The Program (including Contributions) may always be&#xA;Distributed subject to the version of the Agreement under which it was&#xA;received. In addition, after a new version of the Agreement is published,&#xA;Contributor may elect to Distribute the Program (including its&#xA;Contributions) under the new version.&#xA;&#xA;Except as expressly stated in Sections 2(a) and 2(b) above, Recipient&#xA;receives no rights or licenses to the intellectual property of any&#xA;Contributor under this Agreement, whether expressly, by implication,&#xA;estoppel or otherwise. All rights in the Program not expressly granted&#xA;under this Agreement are reserved. Nothing in this Agreement is intended&#xA;to be enforceable by any entity that is not a Contributor or Recipient.&#xA;No third-party beneficiary rights are created under this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;Exhibit A - Form of Secondary Licenses Notice&#xA;&#xA;&quot;This Source Code may also be made available under the following &#xA;Secondary Licenses when the conditions for such availability set forth &#xA;in the Eclipse Public License, v. 2.0 are satisfied: {name license(s),&#xA;version(s), and exceptions or additional permissions here}.&quot;&#xA;&#xA;  Simply including a copy of this Agreement, including this Exhibit A&#xA;  is not sufficient to license the Source Code under Secondary Licenses.&#xA;&#xA;  If it is not possible or desirable to put the notice in a particular&#xA;  file, then You may include the notice in a location (such as a LICENSE&#xA;  file in a relevant directory) where a recipient would be likely to&#xA;  look for such a notice.&#xA;&#xA;  You may add additional accurate notices of copyright ownership.
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='https://github.com/fraunhoferfokus/Xtensions' url='https://github.com/fraunhoferfokus/Xtensions'>
        Copyright (c) 2017 Max Bureck (Fraunhofer FOKUS) and others.&#xA;All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials&#xA;are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v2.0&#xA;which accompanies this distribution, and is available at&#xA;http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v20.html&#xA;&#xA;Contributors:&#xA;Max Bureck (Fraunhofer FOKUS)
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.source.feature.group' version='1.0.0.201711031739' singleton='false'>
      <update id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.source.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,1.0.0.201711031739)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='9'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='Xtensions Feature Developer Resources'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='This library provides utility extension methods, mostly for JDK 8 classes.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='https://github.com/fraunhoferfokus/Xtensions'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='de.fhg.fokus'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
        <property name='maven-groupId' value='de.fhg.fokus'/>
        <property name='maven-artifactId' value='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature'/>
        <property name='maven-version' value='1.0.0-SNAPSHOT'/>
        <property name='maven-classifier' value='sources-feature'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.source.feature.group' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='3'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.feature.group' range='[1.0.0.201711031739,1.0.0.201711031739]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.source' range='[1.0.0.201711031739,1.0.0.201711031739]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.source.feature.jar' range='[1.0.0.201711031739,1.0.0.201711031739]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='https://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v20.html' url='https://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v20.html'>
          Eclipse Public License - v 2.0&#xA;&#xA;    THE ACCOMPANYING PROGRAM IS PROVIDED UNDER THE TERMS OF THIS ECLIPSE&#xA;    PUBLIC LICENSE (&amp;quot;AGREEMENT&amp;quot;). ANY USE, REPRODUCTION OR DISTRIBUTION&#xA;    OF THE PROGRAM CONSTITUTES RECIPIENT&amp;apos;S ACCEPTANCE OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;&#xA;1. DEFINITIONS&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Contribution&amp;quot; means:&#xA;&#xA;  a) in the case of the initial Contributor, the initial content&#xA;     Distributed under this Agreement, and&#xA;&#xA;  b) in the case of each subsequent Contributor:&#xA;     i) changes to the Program, and&#xA;     ii) additions to the Program;&#xA;  where such changes and/or additions to the Program originate from&#xA;  and are Distributed by that particular Contributor. A Contribution&#xA;  &amp;quot;originates&amp;quot; from a Contributor if it was added to the Program by&#xA;  such Contributor itself or anyone acting on such Contributor&amp;apos;s behalf.&#xA;  Contributions do not include changes or additions to the Program that&#xA;  are not Modified Works.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Contributor&amp;quot; means any person or entity that Distributes the Program.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Licensed Patents&amp;quot; mean patent claims licensable by a Contributor which&#xA;are necessarily infringed by the use or sale of its Contribution alone&#xA;or when combined with the Program.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Program&amp;quot; means the Contributions Distributed in accordance with this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Recipient&amp;quot; means anyone who receives the Program under this Agreement&#xA;or any Secondary License (as applicable), including Contributors.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Derivative Works&amp;quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source Code or other&#xA;form, that is based on (or derived from) the Program and for which the&#xA;editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications&#xA;represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Modified Works&amp;quot; shall mean any work in Source Code or other form that&#xA;results from an addition to, deletion from, or modification of the&#xA;contents of the Program, including, for purposes of clarity any new file&#xA;in Source Code form that contains any contents of the Program. Modified&#xA;Works shall not include works that contain only declarations,&#xA;interfaces, types, classes, structures, or files of the Program solely&#xA;in each case in order to link to, bind by name, or subclass the Program&#xA;or Modified Works thereof.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Distribute&amp;quot; means the acts of a) distributing or b) making available&#xA;in any manner that enables the transfer of a copy.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Source Code&amp;quot; means the form of a Program preferred for making&#xA;modifications, including but not limited to software source code,&#xA;documentation source, and configuration files.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;Secondary License&amp;quot; means either the GNU General Public License,&#xA;Version 2.0, or any later versions of that license, including any&#xA;exceptions or additional permissions as identified by the initial&#xA;Contributor.&#xA;&#xA;2. GRANT OF RIGHTS&#xA;&#xA;  a) Subject to the terms of this Agreement, each Contributor hereby&#xA;  grants Recipient a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free copyright&#xA;  license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of, publicly display,&#xA;  publicly perform, Distribute and sublicense the Contribution of such&#xA;  Contributor, if any, and such Derivative Works.&#xA;&#xA;  b) Subject to the terms of this Agreement, each Contributor hereby&#xA;  grants Recipient a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free patent&#xA;  license under Licensed Patents to make, use, sell, offer to sell,&#xA;  import and otherwise transfer the Contribution of such Contributor,&#xA;  if any, in Source Code or other form. This patent license shall&#xA;  apply to the combination of the Contribution and the Program if, at&#xA;  the time the Contribution is added by the Contributor, such addition&#xA;  of the Contribution causes such combination to be covered by the&#xA;  Licensed Patents. The patent license shall not apply to any other&#xA;  combinations which include the Contribution. No hardware per se is&#xA;  licensed hereunder.&#xA;&#xA;  c) Recipient understands that although each Contributor grants the&#xA;  licenses to its Contributions set forth herein, no assurances are&#xA;  provided by any Contributor that the Program does not infringe the&#xA;  patent or other intellectual property rights of any other entity.&#xA;  Each Contributor disclaims any liability to Recipient for claims&#xA;  brought by any other entity based on infringement of intellectual&#xA;  property rights or otherwise. As a condition to exercising the&#xA;  rights and licenses granted hereunder, each Recipient hereby&#xA;  assumes sole responsibility to secure any other intellectual&#xA;  property rights needed, if any. For example, if a third party&#xA;  patent license is required to allow Recipient to Distribute the&#xA;  Program, it is Recipient&amp;apos;s responsibility to acquire that license&#xA;  before distributing the Program.&#xA;&#xA;  d) Each Contributor represents that to its knowledge it has&#xA;  sufficient copyright rights in its Contribution, if any, to grant&#xA;  the copyright license set forth in this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;  e) Notwithstanding the terms of any Secondary License, no&#xA;  Contributor makes additional grants to any Recipient (other than&#xA;  those set forth in this Agreement) as a result of such Recipient&amp;apos;s&#xA;  receipt of the Program under the terms of a Secondary License&#xA;  (if permitted under the terms of Section 3).&#xA;&#xA;3. REQUIREMENTS&#xA;&#xA;3.1 If a Contributor Distributes the Program in any form, then:&#xA;&#xA;  a) the Program must also be made available as Source Code, in&#xA;  accordance with section 3.2, and the Contributor must accompany&#xA;  the Program with a statement that the Source Code for the Program&#xA;  is available under this Agreement, and informs Recipients how to&#xA;  obtain it in a reasonable manner on or through a medium customarily&#xA;  used for software exchange; and&#xA;&#xA;  b) the Contributor may Distribute the Program under a license&#xA;  different than this Agreement, provided that such license:&#xA;     i) effectively disclaims on behalf of all other Contributors all&#xA;     warranties and conditions, express and implied, including&#xA;     warranties or conditions of title and non-infringement, and&#xA;     implied warranties or conditions of merchantability and fitness&#xA;     for a particular purpose;&#xA;&#xA;     ii) effectively excludes on behalf of all other Contributors all&#xA;     liability for damages, including direct, indirect, special,&#xA;     incidental and consequential damages, such as lost profits;&#xA;&#xA;     iii) does not attempt to limit or alter the recipients&amp;apos; rights&#xA;     in the Source Code under section 3.2; and&#xA;&#xA;     iv) requires any subsequent distribution of the Program by any&#xA;     party to be under a license that satisfies the requirements&#xA;     of this section 3.&#xA;&#xA;3.2 When the Program is Distributed as Source Code:&#xA;&#xA;  a) it must be made available under this Agreement, or if the&#xA;  Program (i) is combined with other material in a separate file or&#xA;  files made available under a Secondary License, and (ii) the initial&#xA;  Contributor attached to the Source Code the notice described in&#xA;  Exhibit A of this Agreement, then the Program may be made available&#xA;  under the terms of such Secondary Licenses, and&#xA;&#xA;  b) a copy of this Agreement must be included with each copy of&#xA;  the Program.&#xA;&#xA;3.3 Contributors may not remove or alter any copyright, patent,&#xA;trademark, attribution notices, disclaimers of warranty, or limitations&#xA;of liability (&amp;quot;notices&amp;quot;) contained within the Program from any copy of&#xA;the Program which they Distribute, provided that Contributors may add&#xA;their own appropriate notices.&#xA;&#xA;4. COMMERCIAL DISTRIBUTION&#xA;&#xA;Commercial distributors of software may accept certain responsibilities&#xA;with respect to end users, business partners and the like. While this&#xA;license is intended to facilitate the commercial use of the Program,&#xA;the Contributor who includes the Program in a commercial product&#xA;offering should do so in a manner which does not create potential&#xA;liability for other Contributors. Therefore, if a Contributor includes&#xA;the Program in a commercial product offering, such Contributor&#xA;(&amp;quot;Commercial Contributor&amp;quot;) hereby agrees to defend and indemnify every&#xA;other Contributor (&amp;quot;Indemnified Contributor&amp;quot;) against any losses,&#xA;damages and costs (collectively &amp;quot;Losses&amp;quot;) arising from claims, lawsuits&#xA;and other legal actions brought by a third party against the Indemnified&#xA;Contributor to the extent caused by the acts or omissions of such&#xA;Commercial Contributor in connection with its distribution of the Program&#xA;in a commercial product offering. The obligations in this section do not&#xA;apply to any claims or Losses relating to any actual or alleged&#xA;intellectual property infringement. In order to qualify, an Indemnified&#xA;Contributor must: a) promptly notify the Commercial Contributor in&#xA;writing of such claim, and b) allow the Commercial Contributor to control,&#xA;and cooperate with the Commercial Contributor in, the defense and any&#xA;related settlement negotiations. The Indemnified Contributor may&#xA;participate in any such claim at its own expense.&#xA;&#xA;For example, a Contributor might include the Program in a commercial&#xA;product offering, Product X. That Contributor is then a Commercial&#xA;Contributor. If that Commercial Contributor then makes performance&#xA;claims, or offers warranties related to Product X, those performance&#xA;claims and warranties are such Commercial Contributor&amp;apos;s responsibility&#xA;alone. Under this section, the Commercial Contributor would have to&#xA;defend claims against the other Contributors related to those performance&#xA;claims and warranties, and if a court requires any other Contributor to&#xA;pay any damages as a result, the Commercial Contributor must pay&#xA;those damages.&#xA;&#xA;5. NO WARRANTY&#xA;&#xA;EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH IN THIS AGREEMENT, AND TO THE EXTENT&#xA;PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE PROGRAM IS PROVIDED ON AN &amp;quot;AS IS&amp;quot;&#xA;BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR&#xA;IMPLIED INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF&#xA;TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR&#xA;PURPOSE. Each Recipient is solely responsible for determining the&#xA;appropriateness of using and distributing the Program and assumes all&#xA;risks associated with its exercise of rights under this Agreement,&#xA;including but not limited to the risks and costs of program errors,&#xA;compliance with applicable laws, damage to or loss of data, programs&#xA;or equipment, and unavailability or interruption of operations.&#xA;&#xA;6. DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY&#xA;&#xA;EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH IN THIS AGREEMENT, AND TO THE EXTENT&#xA;PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, NEITHER RECIPIENT NOR ANY CONTRIBUTORS&#xA;SHALL HAVE ANY LIABILITY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL,&#xA;EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LOST&#xA;PROFITS), HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN&#xA;CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE)&#xA;ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OR DISTRIBUTION OF THE PROGRAM OR THE&#xA;EXERCISE OF ANY RIGHTS GRANTED HEREUNDER, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE&#xA;POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.&#xA;&#xA;7. GENERAL&#xA;&#xA;If any provision of this Agreement is invalid or unenforceable under&#xA;applicable law, it shall not affect the validity or enforceability of&#xA;the remainder of the terms of this Agreement, and without further&#xA;action by the parties hereto, such provision shall be reformed to the&#xA;minimum extent necessary to make such provision valid and enforceable.&#xA;&#xA;If Recipient institutes patent litigation against any entity&#xA;(including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the&#xA;Program itself (excluding combinations of the Program with other software&#xA;or hardware) infringes such Recipient&amp;apos;s patent(s), then such Recipient&amp;apos;s&#xA;rights granted under Section 2(b) shall terminate as of the date such&#xA;litigation is filed.&#xA;&#xA;All Recipient&amp;apos;s rights under this Agreement shall terminate if it&#xA;fails to comply with any of the material terms or conditions of this&#xA;Agreement and does not cure such failure in a reasonable period of&#xA;time after becoming aware of such noncompliance. If all Recipient&amp;apos;s&#xA;rights under this Agreement terminate, Recipient agrees to cease use&#xA;and distribution of the Program as soon as reasonably practicable.&#xA;However, Recipient&amp;apos;s obligations under this Agreement and any licenses&#xA;granted by Recipient relating to the Program shall continue and survive.&#xA;&#xA;Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute copies of this Agreement,&#xA;but in order to avoid inconsistency the Agreement is copyrighted and&#xA;may only be modified in the following manner. The Agreement Steward&#xA;reserves the right to publish new versions (including revisions) of&#xA;this Agreement from time to time. No one other than the Agreement&#xA;Steward has the right to modify this Agreement. The Eclipse Foundation&#xA;is the initial Agreement Steward. The Eclipse Foundation may assign the&#xA;responsibility to serve as the Agreement Steward to a suitable separate&#xA;entity. Each new version of the Agreement will be given a distinguishing&#xA;version number. The Program (including Contributions) may always be&#xA;Distributed subject to the version of the Agreement under which it was&#xA;received. In addition, after a new version of the Agreement is published,&#xA;Contributor may elect to Distribute the Program (including its&#xA;Contributions) under the new version.&#xA;&#xA;Except as expressly stated in Sections 2(a) and 2(b) above, Recipient&#xA;receives no rights or licenses to the intellectual property of any&#xA;Contributor under this Agreement, whether expressly, by implication,&#xA;estoppel or otherwise. All rights in the Program not expressly granted&#xA;under this Agreement are reserved. Nothing in this Agreement is intended&#xA;to be enforceable by any entity that is not a Contributor or Recipient.&#xA;No third-party beneficiary rights are created under this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;Exhibit A - Form of Secondary Licenses Notice&#xA;&#xA;&amp;quot;This Source Code may also be made available under the following &#xA;Secondary Licenses when the conditions for such availability set forth &#xA;in the Eclipse Public License, v. 2.0 are satisfied: {name license(s),&#xA;version(s), and exceptions or additional permissions here}.&amp;quot;&#xA;&#xA;  Simply including a copy of this Agreement, including this Exhibit A&#xA;  is not sufficient to license the Source Code under Secondary Licenses.&#xA;&#xA;  If it is not possible or desirable to put the notice in a particular&#xA;  file, then You may include the notice in a location (such as a LICENSE&#xA;  file in a relevant directory) where a recipient would be likely to&#xA;  look for such a notice.&#xA;&#xA;  You may add additional accurate notices of copyright ownership.
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='https://github.com/fraunhoferfokus/Xtensions' url='https://github.com/fraunhoferfokus/Xtensions'>
        Copyright (c) 2017 Max Bureck (Fraunhofer FOKUS) and others.&#xA;All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials&#xA;are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v2.0&#xA;which accompanies this distribution, and is available at&#xA;http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v20.html&#xA;&#xA;Contributors:&#xA;Max Bureck (Fraunhofer FOKUS)
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.eclipse.xtend.lib.macro' version='2.12.0.v20170518-0757' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.eclipse.xtend.lib.macro' range='[0.0.0,2.12.0.v20170518-0757)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='Xtend Macro Interfaces'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='Eclipse Xtext'/>
        <property name='maven-groupId' value='org.eclipse.xtend'/>
        <property name='maven-artifactId' value='org.eclipse.xtend.lib.macro'/>
        <property name='maven-version' value='2.12.0'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='8'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.xtend.lib.macro' version='2.12.0.v20170518-0757'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.xtend.lib.macro' version='2.12.0.v20170518-0757'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.eclipse.xtend.lib.macro' version='2.12.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.eclipse.xtend.lib.macro.declaration' version='2.12.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.eclipse.xtend.lib.macro.expression' version='2.12.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.eclipse.xtend.lib.macro.file' version='2.12.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.eclipse.xtend.lib.macro.services' version='2.12.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='1'>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.xtext.xbase.lib' range='0.0.0'/>
      </requires>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.eclipse.xtend.lib.macro' version='2.12.0.v20170518-0757'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: org.eclipse.xtend.lib.macro&#xA;Bundle-Version: 2.12.0.v20170518-0757
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.feature.group' version='1.0.0.201711031739' singleton='false'>
      <update id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,1.0.0.201711031739)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='8'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='Xtensions Feature'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='This library provides utility extension methods, mostly for JDK 8 classes.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='https://github.com/fraunhoferfokus/Xtensions'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='de.fhg.fokus'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
        <property name='maven-groupId' value='de.fhg.fokus'/>
        <property name='maven-artifactId' value='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature'/>
        <property name='maven-version' value='1.0.0-SNAPSHOT'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.feature.group' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='2'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions' range='[1.0.0.201711031739,1.0.0.201711031739]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.feature.feature.jar' range='[1.0.0.201711031739,1.0.0.201711031739]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='https://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v20.html' url='https://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v20.html'>
          Eclipse Public License - v 2.0&#xA;&#xA;    THE ACCOMPANYING PROGRAM IS PROVIDED UNDER THE TERMS OF THIS ECLIPSE&#xA;    PUBLIC LICENSE (&quot;AGREEMENT&quot;). ANY USE, REPRODUCTION OR DISTRIBUTION&#xA;    OF THE PROGRAM CONSTITUTES RECIPIENT&apos;S ACCEPTANCE OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;&#xA;1. DEFINITIONS&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; means:&#xA;&#xA;  a) in the case of the initial Contributor, the initial content&#xA;     Distributed under this Agreement, and&#xA;&#xA;  b) in the case of each subsequent Contributor:&#xA;     i) changes to the Program, and&#xA;     ii) additions to the Program;&#xA;  where such changes and/or additions to the Program originate from&#xA;  and are Distributed by that particular Contributor. A Contribution&#xA;  &quot;originates&quot; from a Contributor if it was added to the Program by&#xA;  such Contributor itself or anyone acting on such Contributor&apos;s behalf.&#xA;  Contributions do not include changes or additions to the Program that&#xA;  are not Modified Works.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; means any person or entity that Distributes the Program.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Licensed Patents&quot; mean patent claims licensable by a Contributor which&#xA;are necessarily infringed by the use or sale of its Contribution alone&#xA;or when combined with the Program.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Program&quot; means the Contributions Distributed in accordance with this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Recipient&quot; means anyone who receives the Program under this Agreement&#xA;or any Secondary License (as applicable), including Contributors.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source Code or other&#xA;form, that is based on (or derived from) the Program and for which the&#xA;editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications&#xA;represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Modified Works&quot; shall mean any work in Source Code or other form that&#xA;results from an addition to, deletion from, or modification of the&#xA;contents of the Program, including, for purposes of clarity any new file&#xA;in Source Code form that contains any contents of the Program. Modified&#xA;Works shall not include works that contain only declarations,&#xA;interfaces, types, classes, structures, or files of the Program solely&#xA;in each case in order to link to, bind by name, or subclass the Program&#xA;or Modified Works thereof.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Distribute&quot; means the acts of a) distributing or b) making available&#xA;in any manner that enables the transfer of a copy.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Source Code&quot; means the form of a Program preferred for making&#xA;modifications, including but not limited to software source code,&#xA;documentation source, and configuration files.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Secondary License&quot; means either the GNU General Public License,&#xA;Version 2.0, or any later versions of that license, including any&#xA;exceptions or additional permissions as identified by the initial&#xA;Contributor.&#xA;&#xA;2. GRANT OF RIGHTS&#xA;&#xA;  a) Subject to the terms of this Agreement, each Contributor hereby&#xA;  grants Recipient a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free copyright&#xA;  license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of, publicly display,&#xA;  publicly perform, Distribute and sublicense the Contribution of such&#xA;  Contributor, if any, and such Derivative Works.&#xA;&#xA;  b) Subject to the terms of this Agreement, each Contributor hereby&#xA;  grants Recipient a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free patent&#xA;  license under Licensed Patents to make, use, sell, offer to sell,&#xA;  import and otherwise transfer the Contribution of such Contributor,&#xA;  if any, in Source Code or other form. This patent license shall&#xA;  apply to the combination of the Contribution and the Program if, at&#xA;  the time the Contribution is added by the Contributor, such addition&#xA;  of the Contribution causes such combination to be covered by the&#xA;  Licensed Patents. The patent license shall not apply to any other&#xA;  combinations which include the Contribution. No hardware per se is&#xA;  licensed hereunder.&#xA;&#xA;  c) Recipient understands that although each Contributor grants the&#xA;  licenses to its Contributions set forth herein, no assurances are&#xA;  provided by any Contributor that the Program does not infringe the&#xA;  patent or other intellectual property rights of any other entity.&#xA;  Each Contributor disclaims any liability to Recipient for claims&#xA;  brought by any other entity based on infringement of intellectual&#xA;  property rights or otherwise. As a condition to exercising the&#xA;  rights and licenses granted hereunder, each Recipient hereby&#xA;  assumes sole responsibility to secure any other intellectual&#xA;  property rights needed, if any. For example, if a third party&#xA;  patent license is required to allow Recipient to Distribute the&#xA;  Program, it is Recipient&apos;s responsibility to acquire that license&#xA;  before distributing the Program.&#xA;&#xA;  d) Each Contributor represents that to its knowledge it has&#xA;  sufficient copyright rights in its Contribution, if any, to grant&#xA;  the copyright license set forth in this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;  e) Notwithstanding the terms of any Secondary License, no&#xA;  Contributor makes additional grants to any Recipient (other than&#xA;  those set forth in this Agreement) as a result of such Recipient&apos;s&#xA;  receipt of the Program under the terms of a Secondary License&#xA;  (if permitted under the terms of Section 3).&#xA;&#xA;3. REQUIREMENTS&#xA;&#xA;3.1 If a Contributor Distributes the Program in any form, then:&#xA;&#xA;  a) the Program must also be made available as Source Code, in&#xA;  accordance with section 3.2, and the Contributor must accompany&#xA;  the Program with a statement that the Source Code for the Program&#xA;  is available under this Agreement, and informs Recipients how to&#xA;  obtain it in a reasonable manner on or through a medium customarily&#xA;  used for software exchange; and&#xA;&#xA;  b) the Contributor may Distribute the Program under a license&#xA;  different than this Agreement, provided that such license:&#xA;     i) effectively disclaims on behalf of all other Contributors all&#xA;     warranties and conditions, express and implied, including&#xA;     warranties or conditions of title and non-infringement, and&#xA;     implied warranties or conditions of merchantability and fitness&#xA;     for a particular purpose;&#xA;&#xA;     ii) effectively excludes on behalf of all other Contributors all&#xA;     liability for damages, including direct, indirect, special,&#xA;     incidental and consequential damages, such as lost profits;&#xA;&#xA;     iii) does not attempt to limit or alter the recipients&apos; rights&#xA;     in the Source Code under section 3.2; and&#xA;&#xA;     iv) requires any subsequent distribution of the Program by any&#xA;     party to be under a license that satisfies the requirements&#xA;     of this section 3.&#xA;&#xA;3.2 When the Program is Distributed as Source Code:&#xA;&#xA;  a) it must be made available under this Agreement, or if the&#xA;  Program (i) is combined with other material in a separate file or&#xA;  files made available under a Secondary License, and (ii) the initial&#xA;  Contributor attached to the Source Code the notice described in&#xA;  Exhibit A of this Agreement, then the Program may be made available&#xA;  under the terms of such Secondary Licenses, and&#xA;&#xA;  b) a copy of this Agreement must be included with each copy of&#xA;  the Program.&#xA;&#xA;3.3 Contributors may not remove or alter any copyright, patent,&#xA;trademark, attribution notices, disclaimers of warranty, or limitations&#xA;of liability (&quot;notices&quot;) contained within the Program from any copy of&#xA;the Program which they Distribute, provided that Contributors may add&#xA;their own appropriate notices.&#xA;&#xA;4. COMMERCIAL DISTRIBUTION&#xA;&#xA;Commercial distributors of software may accept certain responsibilities&#xA;with respect to end users, business partners and the like. While this&#xA;license is intended to facilitate the commercial use of the Program,&#xA;the Contributor who includes the Program in a commercial product&#xA;offering should do so in a manner which does not create potential&#xA;liability for other Contributors. Therefore, if a Contributor includes&#xA;the Program in a commercial product offering, such Contributor&#xA;(&quot;Commercial Contributor&quot;) hereby agrees to defend and indemnify every&#xA;other Contributor (&quot;Indemnified Contributor&quot;) against any losses,&#xA;damages and costs (collectively &quot;Losses&quot;) arising from claims, lawsuits&#xA;and other legal actions brought by a third party against the Indemnified&#xA;Contributor to the extent caused by the acts or omissions of such&#xA;Commercial Contributor in connection with its distribution of the Program&#xA;in a commercial product offering. The obligations in this section do not&#xA;apply to any claims or Losses relating to any actual or alleged&#xA;intellectual property infringement. In order to qualify, an Indemnified&#xA;Contributor must: a) promptly notify the Commercial Contributor in&#xA;writing of such claim, and b) allow the Commercial Contributor to control,&#xA;and cooperate with the Commercial Contributor in, the defense and any&#xA;related settlement negotiations. The Indemnified Contributor may&#xA;participate in any such claim at its own expense.&#xA;&#xA;For example, a Contributor might include the Program in a commercial&#xA;product offering, Product X. That Contributor is then a Commercial&#xA;Contributor. If that Commercial Contributor then makes performance&#xA;claims, or offers warranties related to Product X, those performance&#xA;claims and warranties are such Commercial Contributor&apos;s responsibility&#xA;alone. Under this section, the Commercial Contributor would have to&#xA;defend claims against the other Contributors related to those performance&#xA;claims and warranties, and if a court requires any other Contributor to&#xA;pay any damages as a result, the Commercial Contributor must pay&#xA;those damages.&#xA;&#xA;5. NO WARRANTY&#xA;&#xA;EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH IN THIS AGREEMENT, AND TO THE EXTENT&#xA;PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE PROGRAM IS PROVIDED ON AN &quot;AS IS&quot;&#xA;BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR&#xA;IMPLIED INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF&#xA;TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR&#xA;PURPOSE. Each Recipient is solely responsible for determining the&#xA;appropriateness of using and distributing the Program and assumes all&#xA;risks associated with its exercise of rights under this Agreement,&#xA;including but not limited to the risks and costs of program errors,&#xA;compliance with applicable laws, damage to or loss of data, programs&#xA;or equipment, and unavailability or interruption of operations.&#xA;&#xA;6. DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY&#xA;&#xA;EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH IN THIS AGREEMENT, AND TO THE EXTENT&#xA;PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, NEITHER RECIPIENT NOR ANY CONTRIBUTORS&#xA;SHALL HAVE ANY LIABILITY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL,&#xA;EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LOST&#xA;PROFITS), HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN&#xA;CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE)&#xA;ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OR DISTRIBUTION OF THE PROGRAM OR THE&#xA;EXERCISE OF ANY RIGHTS GRANTED HEREUNDER, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE&#xA;POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.&#xA;&#xA;7. GENERAL&#xA;&#xA;If any provision of this Agreement is invalid or unenforceable under&#xA;applicable law, it shall not affect the validity or enforceability of&#xA;the remainder of the terms of this Agreement, and without further&#xA;action by the parties hereto, such provision shall be reformed to the&#xA;minimum extent necessary to make such provision valid and enforceable.&#xA;&#xA;If Recipient institutes patent litigation against any entity&#xA;(including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the&#xA;Program itself (excluding combinations of the Program with other software&#xA;or hardware) infringes such Recipient&apos;s patent(s), then such Recipient&apos;s&#xA;rights granted under Section 2(b) shall terminate as of the date such&#xA;litigation is filed.&#xA;&#xA;All Recipient&apos;s rights under this Agreement shall terminate if it&#xA;fails to comply with any of the material terms or conditions of this&#xA;Agreement and does not cure such failure in a reasonable period of&#xA;time after becoming aware of such noncompliance. If all Recipient&apos;s&#xA;rights under this Agreement terminate, Recipient agrees to cease use&#xA;and distribution of the Program as soon as reasonably practicable.&#xA;However, Recipient&apos;s obligations under this Agreement and any licenses&#xA;granted by Recipient relating to the Program shall continue and survive.&#xA;&#xA;Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute copies of this Agreement,&#xA;but in order to avoid inconsistency the Agreement is copyrighted and&#xA;may only be modified in the following manner. The Agreement Steward&#xA;reserves the right to publish new versions (including revisions) of&#xA;this Agreement from time to time. No one other than the Agreement&#xA;Steward has the right to modify this Agreement. The Eclipse Foundation&#xA;is the initial Agreement Steward. The Eclipse Foundation may assign the&#xA;responsibility to serve as the Agreement Steward to a suitable separate&#xA;entity. Each new version of the Agreement will be given a distinguishing&#xA;version number. The Program (including Contributions) may always be&#xA;Distributed subject to the version of the Agreement under which it was&#xA;received. In addition, after a new version of the Agreement is published,&#xA;Contributor may elect to Distribute the Program (including its&#xA;Contributions) under the new version.&#xA;&#xA;Except as expressly stated in Sections 2(a) and 2(b) above, Recipient&#xA;receives no rights or licenses to the intellectual property of any&#xA;Contributor under this Agreement, whether expressly, by implication,&#xA;estoppel or otherwise. All rights in the Program not expressly granted&#xA;under this Agreement are reserved. Nothing in this Agreement is intended&#xA;to be enforceable by any entity that is not a Contributor or Recipient.&#xA;No third-party beneficiary rights are created under this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;Exhibit A - Form of Secondary Licenses Notice&#xA;&#xA;&quot;This Source Code may also be made available under the following &#xA;Secondary Licenses when the conditions for such availability set forth &#xA;in the Eclipse Public License, v. 2.0 are satisfied: {name license(s),&#xA;version(s), and exceptions or additional permissions here}.&quot;&#xA;&#xA;  Simply including a copy of this Agreement, including this Exhibit A&#xA;  is not sufficient to license the Source Code under Secondary Licenses.&#xA;&#xA;  If it is not possible or desirable to put the notice in a particular&#xA;  file, then You may include the notice in a location (such as a LICENSE&#xA;  file in a relevant directory) where a recipient would be likely to&#xA;  look for such a notice.&#xA;&#xA;  You may add additional accurate notices of copyright ownership.
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='https://github.com/fraunhoferfokus/Xtensions' url='https://github.com/fraunhoferfokus/Xtensions'>
        Copyright (c) 2017 Max Bureck (Fraunhofer FOKUS) and others.&#xA;All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials&#xA;are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v2.0&#xA;which accompanies this distribution, and is available at&#xA;http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v20.html&#xA;&#xA;Contributors:&#xA;Max Bureck (Fraunhofer FOKUS)
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions' version='1.0.0.201711031739' singleton='false'>
      <update id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions' range='[0.0.0,1.0.0.201711031739)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='Xtenders'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='Fraunhofer FOKUS'/>
        <property name='maven-groupId' value='de.fhg.fokus'/>
        <property name='maven-artifactId' value='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions'/>
        <property name='maven-version' value='1.0.0-SNAPSHOT'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='12'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.concurrent' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.datetime' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.function' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.iteration' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.optional' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.pair' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.range' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.stream' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions.string' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='3'>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.xtend.lib' range='2.8.4'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.jdt.annotation' range='[2.0.0,3.0.0)' optional='true' greedy='false'/>
        <required namespace='java.package' name='org.eclipse.jdt.annotation' range='0.0.0' optional='true' greedy='false'/>
      </requires>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='de.fhg.fokus.xtensions' version='1.0.0.201711031739'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: de.fhg.fokus.xtensions&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.0.0.201711031739
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
  </units>
</repository>
